{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Solar Panel Installers","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","__cache./api/resource/task/40300/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40300,"taskName":"Solar Panels For Electric System - Install","taskDescription":"Install Solar Panels For Electric System","xmTaskDescriptor":"Solar Panel Installers","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":227,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Electrical Solar Panel PV sun","textMessagingName":"Inst Solar Panels","rolloverLongDesc":"Done by solar specialists. Solar Panel systems use arrays of photovoltaic power cells to convert sunlight into electricity.","rolloverShortDesc":"Solar panels forl electrical systems.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Install or Replace Solar Panels/Electric Systems. HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened solar panel installation contractors in your area.","htmlTitle":"Solar Panel Installation \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Install Solar Panels","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":102,"acceptGoal":4,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":3,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Solar Panel For Electric System Installation","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Solar Panels For Electric System - Install","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Solar Panel Project","urlName":"Solar-Panels-Install-or-Replace","taskConsiderationId":3,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Solar Panel Installation Companies - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Costs \u0026 Reviews","searchKeywords":"panels, energy, efficient, green, sun, cell","emcCategoryOid":-14820,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":600,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40300/":{"taskOID":40300,"originalTaskOID":40300,"setID":600,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":6897,"questionDisplayText":"Kind of solar panel system","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of solar panel electric system do you want?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":8028,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Grid tie-in (no battery backup)","answerDisplayText":"Grid tie-in (no battery backup)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8029,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Grid tie-in (battery backup)","answerDisplayText":"Grid tie-in (battery backup)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8030,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Off grid with battery backup","answerDisplayText":"Off grid with battery backup","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8031,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Want recommendation","answerDisplayText":"Want recommendation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502147,"questionDisplayText":"Sun Exposure","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Approximately, how much sun exposure does the property get?","shortQuestionText":"Approximately, how much sun exposure does the property get?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":202995,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Full sun","answerDisplayText":"Full sun","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":202996,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Partial sun","answerDisplayText":"Partial sun","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":202997,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Mostly shaded","answerDisplayText":"Mostly shaded","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4295,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Not sure","answerDisplayText":"Not sure","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502164,"questionDisplayText":"Utility Provider","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Who is your current utility provider (if known)?","shortQuestionText":"Who is your current utility provider (if known)?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":0,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"NA","answerDisplayText":"NA","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"text","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502165,"questionDisplayText":"Approximate Monthly Bill","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Approximately, what is your average monthly electric bill?","shortQuestionText":"Approximately, what is your average monthly electric bill?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":3538,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Less than $100","answerDisplayText":"Less than $100","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":202985,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"$100 - $149","answerDisplayText":"$100 - $149","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":202986,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"$150 - $199","answerDisplayText":"$150 - $199","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":202987,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"$200 - $249","answerDisplayText":"$200 - $249","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":202988,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"$250 - $299","answerDisplayText":"$250 - $299","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":202989,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"$300 - $349 ","answerDisplayText":"$300 - $349 ","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":202990,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"More than $350","answerDisplayText":"More than $350","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4295,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Not sure","answerDisplayText":"Not sure","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502145,"questionDisplayText":"Approximate square footage ","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What is the approximate square footage of the area the system will serve? ","shortQuestionText":"What is the approximate square footage of the area the system will serve? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":202991,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Less than 1,000 sq ft","answerDisplayText":"Less than 1,000 sq ft","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":202992,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"1,000 - 2,000 sq ft","answerDisplayText":"1,000 - 2,000 sq ft","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":202993,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"2,000 - 3,000 sq ft","answerDisplayText":"2,000 - 3,000 sq ft","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":202994,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 3,000 sq ft","answerDisplayText":"More than 3,000 sq ft","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502146,"questionDisplayText":"# of Stories","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"How many stories is the building this system will serve? ","shortQuestionText":"How many stories is the building this system will serve? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":9817,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"One story","answerDisplayText":"One story","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9818,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Two stories","answerDisplayText":"Two stories","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9819,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Three stories or more","answerDisplayText":"Three stories or more","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":202964,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within a few weeks","answerDisplayText":"Within a few weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":202965,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Within a month","answerDisplayText":"Within a month","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":202966,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Within a few months","answerDisplayText":"Within a few months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":6897,"questionDisplayText":"Kind of solar panel system","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of solar panel electric system do you want?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":8028,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Grid tie-in (no battery backup)","answerDisplayText":"Grid tie-in (no battery backup)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8029,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Grid tie-in (battery backup)","answerDisplayText":"Grid tie-in (battery backup)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8030,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Off grid with battery backup","answerDisplayText":"Off grid with battery backup","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8031,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Want recommendation","answerDisplayText":"Want recommendation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":8028,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Grid tie-in (no battery backup)","answerDisplayText":"Grid tie-in (no battery backup)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8029,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Grid tie-in (battery backup)","answerDisplayText":"Grid tie-in (battery backup)","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8030,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Off grid with battery backup","answerDisplayText":"Off grid with battery backup","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":8031,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Want recommendation","answerDisplayText":"Want recommendation","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502147,"questionDisplayText":"Sun Exposure","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Approximately, how much sun exposure does the property get?","shortQuestionText":"Approximately, how much sun exposure does the property get?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":202995,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Full sun","answerDisplayText":"Full sun","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":202996,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Partial sun","answerDisplayText":"Partial sun","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":202997,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Mostly shaded","answerDisplayText":"Mostly shaded","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4295,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Not sure","answerDisplayText":"Not sure","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":202995,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Full sun","answerDisplayText":"Full sun","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":202996,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Partial sun","answerDisplayText":"Partial sun","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":202997,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Mostly shaded","answerDisplayText":"Mostly shaded","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4295,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Not sure","answerDisplayText":"Not sure","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502164,"questionDisplayText":"Utility Provider","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Who is your current utility provider (if known)?","shortQuestionText":"Who is your current utility provider (if known)?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":0,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"NA","answerDisplayText":"NA","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"text","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":0,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"NA","answerDisplayText":"NA","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"text","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502165,"questionDisplayText":"Approximate Monthly Bill","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Approximately, what is your average monthly electric bill?","shortQuestionText":"Approximately, what is your average monthly electric bill?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":3538,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Less than $100","answerDisplayText":"Less than $100","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":202985,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"$100 - $149","answerDisplayText":"$100 - $149","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":202986,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"$150 - $199","answerDisplayText":"$150 - $199","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":202987,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"$200 - $249","answerDisplayText":"$200 - $249","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":202988,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"$250 - $299","answerDisplayText":"$250 - $299","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":202989,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"$300 - $349 ","answerDisplayText":"$300 - $349 ","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":202990,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"More than $350","answerDisplayText":"More than $350","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4295,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Not sure","answerDisplayText":"Not sure","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":3538,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Less than $100","answerDisplayText":"Less than $100","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":202985,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"$100 - $149","answerDisplayText":"$100 - $149","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":202986,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"$150 - $199","answerDisplayText":"$150 - $199","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":202987,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"$200 - $249","answerDisplayText":"$200 - $249","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":202988,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"$250 - $299","answerDisplayText":"$250 - $299","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":202989,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"$300 - $349 ","answerDisplayText":"$300 - $349 ","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":202990,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"More than $350","answerDisplayText":"More than $350","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4295,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Not sure","answerDisplayText":"Not sure","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502145,"questionDisplayText":"Approximate square footage ","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What is the approximate square footage of the area the system will serve? ","shortQuestionText":"What is the approximate square footage of the area the system will serve? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":202991,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Less than 1,000 sq ft","answerDisplayText":"Less than 1,000 sq ft","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":202992,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"1,000 - 2,000 sq ft","answerDisplayText":"1,000 - 2,000 sq ft","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":202993,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"2,000 - 3,000 sq ft","answerDisplayText":"2,000 - 3,000 sq ft","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":202994,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 3,000 sq ft","answerDisplayText":"More than 3,000 sq ft","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":202991,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Less than 1,000 sq ft","answerDisplayText":"Less than 1,000 sq ft","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":202992,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"1,000 - 2,000 sq ft","answerDisplayText":"1,000 - 2,000 sq ft","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":202993,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"2,000 - 3,000 sq ft","answerDisplayText":"2,000 - 3,000 sq ft","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":202994,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 3,000 sq ft","answerDisplayText":"More than 3,000 sq ft","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502146,"questionDisplayText":"# of Stories","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"How many stories is the building this system will serve? ","shortQuestionText":"How many stories is the building this system will serve? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":9817,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"One story","answerDisplayText":"One story","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9818,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Two stories","answerDisplayText":"Two stories","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9819,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Three stories or more","answerDisplayText":"Three stories or more","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":9817,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"One story","answerDisplayText":"One story","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9818,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Two stories","answerDisplayText":"Two stories","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":9819,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Three stories or more","answerDisplayText":"Three stories or more","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":202964,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within a few weeks","answerDisplayText":"Within a few weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":202965,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Within a month","answerDisplayText":"Within a month","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":202966,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Within a few months","answerDisplayText":"Within a few months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":202964,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within a few weeks","answerDisplayText":"Within a few weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":202965,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Within a month","answerDisplayText":"Within a month","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":202966,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Within a few months","answerDisplayText":"Within a few months","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":5,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":502713,"questionDisplayText":"Are you interested in financing?","displayToSP":false,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you interested in financing?","shortQuestionText":"Are you interested in financing?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}